QuranCode 1433
==============

                        اللهُمَّ صَلِّ على مُحَمَّدٍ وءالِ مُحَمَّدٍ                 

                       QuranCode 1433
                   Quran Research Platform
                     ©2011-2014 Ali Adams
                      www.qurancode.com


QuranCode is a numerical and similarity research tool for the ever-revealing book
(Al-Quran Al-Kareem القرءان الكريم) that is readable despite being encrypted.
See http://heliwave.com/EncryptedQuran.pdf for the encryption evidence.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Initial Letter Sentences					جمل مكونة من الحروف المقطعة
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Perfect Text with a Decisive Secret.				نص حكيم له سر قاطع
Ali is a Path to the Truth we follow.				علي صراط حق نمسكه
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Use the InitialLetters tool to generate all 51773 sentences using Quran words only.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

STARTING OPTIONS:
	Standard Edition	Start normally for original and simplified text.
	Lite Edition		Start with SHIFT for essential features only.
	Grammar Edition		Start with CTRL for word-by-word grammar.
	Research Edition	Start with CTRL+SHIFT for advanced research methods and C# scripting.

Primalogy is a new letter-value system derived from surat Al-Fatiha which is built upon
prime numbers (7 verses, 29 words, 139 letters) and is confirmed by surat Al-Ikhlaass,
ayat Al-Kursi, aya Al-Rahmaan, and the word "الله". See http://heliwave.com/Primalogy.pdf.

If you find QuranCode useful, please recite Quran 27:62 a prime number of times (preferably 313)
to bring forward the arrival of Imam Al-Mehdi (as) to restore peace and justice to the crying Earth.
أعوذ بالله من الشيطٰن الرجيم     بِسْمِ ٱللَّهِ ٱلرَّحْمَٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
أَمَّن يُجِيبُ ٱلْمُضْطَرَّ إِذَا دَعَاهُ وَيَكْشِفُ ٱلسُّوٓءَ وَيَجْعَلُكُمْ خُلَفَآءَ ٱلْأَرْضِ ۗ أَءِلَٰهٌۭ مَّعَ ٱللَّهِ ۚ قَلِيلًۭا مَّا تَذَكَّرُونَ
"Who answers the call of the distressed when he invokes Him and removes his distress,
and makes you viceroys of the earth? Is there a god besides Allah? How little do you remember?"

where Allah reminds us of our oath to Him in Quran 7:172
أعوذ بالله من الشيطٰن الرجيم     بِسْمِ ٱللَّهِ ٱلرَّحْمَٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
وَإِذْ أَخَذَ رَبُّكَ مِنۢ بَنِىٓ ءَادَمَ مِن ظُهُورِهِمْ ذُرِّيَّتَهُمْ 
وَأَشْهَدَهُمْ عَلَىٰٓ أَنفُسِهِمْ أَلَسْتُ بِرَبِّكُمْ ۖ قَالُوا۟ بَلَىٰ ۛ شَهِدْنَآ
أَن تَقُولُوا۟ يَوْمَ ٱلْقِيَٰمَةِ إِنَّا كُنَّا عَنْ هَٰذَا غَٰفِلِينَ
"And (remember) when thy Lord brought forth from the Children of Adam, from their reins, their seed,
and made them testify of themselves, (saying): Am I not your Lord? They said: Yea, verily. We testify.
(That was) lest ye should say at the Day of Resurrection: Lo! of this we were unaware."

and where the viceroys of the earth are foretold in Quran 21:105
أعوذ بالله من الشيطٰن الرجيم     بِسْمِ ٱللَّهِ ٱلرَّحْمَٰنِ ٱلرَّحِيمِ
وَلَقَدْ كَتَبْنَا فِى ٱلزَّبُورِ مِنۢ بَعْدِ ٱلذِّكْرِ أَنَّ ٱلْأَرْضَ يَرِثُهَا عِبَادِىَ ٱلصَّٰلِحُونَ
"And verily we have written in the Palms beyond the Reminder: My righteous servants will inherit the earth"

Be a guiding light!

Ali Adams
www.heliwave.com
God > infinity
